we took a bullet train to the future in
this video we are finally leaving guango
to explore another Chinese City and this
time is to a place some of called the
city of the future so join our adventure
as we Zoom across guong like a bullet
experiencing the light delicious food
and The Eccentric atmosphere of
shenzen you're saying live streaming a
live streamer while you're live
streaming what live stream setion
welcome to the guango railway station
South the South guango Railway Station
not the East not the railway station The
South was there a North I don't know
there might be probably west west side
is that a are we going to get shot next
time we go to La we might we are heading
out of guango I mean we had plans we
were going to go to fan we weren't able
to go to Fan we're going to go to dongan
we're not able to go to donguan we could
but it would probably be a whole process
we'd have to go to the donguan railroad
station railway station and then metro
into the City metro back out and then go
to shenzen so we're just going to go
straight to shenzen we are taking a
Chinese bullet train for the first time
all the way to shenzen nice 30 minute
ride easy peasy the ticket process was
interesting we tried to buy the tickets
from the ticket machine machine over
there and it was in all Chinese and then
once we figured out which ones we needed
you needed a Chinese document and buying
them online was a bit hard because they
kept selling out and alip pay the Wi-Fi
and all that stuff was a bit weird but
my gosh it's busy in here and they are
selling out the day after Chinese New
Year few days after Chinese New Year is
popping in here everyone's going home so
let's try to experience a bullet train
in China we've never been on a bullet
train before or only in Italy oh yeah
true only in Italy never in the the Asia
bullet train which is where they're
known for bullet trains so let's just
see how it is can it be better than
train Italia which apparently is like
one of the best in the world so uh well
we don't have to reserve our seats on
this we don't know that yet it would
have been a Chinese there'll be some
Chinese man that comes up like our
Italian man just
like he breathe he he was breathing
really heavy when we were trying to when
we had to pay him he's really
[Music]
angry we bought our tickets half an hour
early is usually train stations you can
get on the train within 30 minutes I
don't know if we're going to make it
there is so many people here it's
unreasonable it's insane
this is a massive City though 15 plus
million people I
think I cannot believe how many people
are here though training in China
luckily our line for checkin was nice
and quick no one's going to shenzen I
guess not too many people we got in they
just It's associated with your passport
I guess cuz we didn't have a ticket we
didn't have a QR code we didn't have
anything and they just stand our
passport and b a big b boom we got it
security was kind of scary how the heck
do we find our seat we're in Carriage 14
oh so all the way down at the end so the
opposite direction we're going we're
heading up towards first class I bet
look at this
baby the pure
might of the bullet train it's shaped
like a l long bullet it's called a
bullet train because of the shape right
not the speed oh yeah I think so looks
like a a 45 caliber oh yeah yes I mean
look at this station hopefully that
Chinese doesn't say don't walk past this
point it probably just says something
along those
lines we're way down second class
Carriage
14 a bullet train it's it's been years
it has been a long time let's get on
this fracking train I'm kind of excited
and I'm excited to see shenzen
is there a lot more people down
here holy nuts this thing is long this
is the longest bullet I've ever seen wow
we're pushing
it if it leaves 2 minutes early we're
screwed we're still on
seven if you see it start closing shove
your arm in the door no matter what it
might bullet away with your clamped arm
though H maybe we should jump in I don't
like that these guys are sitting like
acting like it's going to leave at any
moment slower
walk all right back
out bathroom
off watching station and drinking
water that's cool that's nice bathroom
is a bit small seems like it could use a
wash but it has it that's
nice I don't know what class we're in
right
now but there's trade tables are we in
the back of the train sir we might be
all the way in the back we did get like
probably some of the last tickets
[Music]
this is such a long
train 14
finally bullet train we got we just in
time basically this we literally sat
down and
then it started oh no when is it going
to Bullet I don't know I'm waiting
patiently I want it to be like a roller
coaster where it
just look at that this station's really
cool there's another little like
business distri down
here there some little
mountains on this
side Will Smith what are you doing
here oh look at those weird buildings
down there that is all exactly the same
height we're revving so we have a ke
that we cannot understand luggage
space a table the luggage space is nice
too cuz usually our big bags don't fit
on train luggage no Ur
housing it's a second class seat you
don't get too many amenities and it's
only a 30-minute ride so it'll be
interesting to see the nature out here
too look at this leg room though leg
room is leg room is typically an issue
on budget planes like my knees are
usually up against so if you compare
this to a budget plane that's where the
seat would be trains are usually good I
can't recall do any Trains being too
tight look but buses that's another
problem trains are a comfortable way of
traveling I feel like it is the most
comfortable way to travel even though it
may take a little longer than a plane uh
buses can be crammed and very bumpy
trains are nice and smooth depending on
what country you're in like this one is
very smooth
how fast is this supposed to get I mean
it's not as it's not that far of a
distance so we can't get that fast right
it kind of feels quick it's not like a
plane or a train slower train where it
feels like you're not moving I feel like
we're moving fast cuz we're still slowly
accelerating by slowly I mean like a
kilometer per hour per second oh this is
weird it has
a are we tilted right now yeah we are we
are definitely tilted we're going to
slowly fall into this
River oh look at a little W I thought
that was a carnival but it looks like
it's a playground oh no it's a roller
coaster what the
heck we'll see how fast we're going to
get the fastest I've ever drove a car
was like 212 km an hour you were a
bullet
train oh it stopped oh no it's going
it's going up slower now peek around 320
I bet 328 is my guess oh they changed
the thing they're not impressed by it
anymore all right so they stopped
showing it at
306 all it'll show up again
5,000 every we look outside it would
just be streets of light going by I
don't feel the accelerating as much
anymore yeah no kind of seems like we're
cruising interesting experience been
through a little fire
are we going to die oh it went down it's
going down
now I see I it does kind of feel like
we're decelerating now hopefully you
guys enjoy the confusion of us trying to
figure out the speed of our bullet train
we can't handle the modernness of oh wow
he really breaked right
there all right let's enjoy the
ride Mountain
we're
here welcome to Shan fellow the most
futuristic city ever in the world we
took a bullet train to get here so it's
a good start now if there isn't a
cleaning Street robot that's turned off
when we go out there I'm going to be so
pissed or a self-driving
bus
please sh fren
[Music]
Zen Zenyatta would be impressed by
shenzen Tranquility dude we're going to
have to slowly nudge our way into
here he almost forgot the
snacks how did you almost forget the
snacks the massive bag of Snackies dude
that's so important to this travel they
were taking it all the way up to the
front I don't know what they were going
to do with it but eat it probably almost
missed it time for the
sticks oh man I'm seeing some graded
ceiling up here this is going to be
fancy is this the one that is fancy I
think so or might not be this one it
might be the shenen normal railway
station I know one of the Metro stations
is really fancy is it Bay because Bay
would make the coolest one Bay right saw
dude we're going to get out of here and
we're going to go check into our hotel
the cheapest hotel in shenzen
about uh an interesting one we were
we're a bit scared about this one only
one way to see if it's good or not let's
where and
go overall the bullet train experience
was good it was quick it was easy I
didn't think it was going to make a stop
but it did make a stop about halfway
through there was a bit of a line for
security but it was close yeah yeah we
literally bought it like 30 40 minutes
early at the train station so and they
had e ticketing things there so like
most train stations do so you can just
show up and buy them pretty easily and
it would be much easier if you're
Chinese yeah yeah cuz you could use your
ID and you wouldn't have to go through
like when you check in you wouldn't have
to do a self check in like have somebody
check it for you and stuff yeah it
definitely helps to have a Chinese
number and be Chinese when you're
traveling in China and read and speak
Chinese yeah that usually helps to but
everything has worked so far it's just
been uh sometimes it's been a bit of a
struggle oh we have to scan to get out
too well go over to this one we can't go
into the nice fancy ones we got to go to
the line for the
pwds determination
yes new city new
possibilities and a new Metro
some glass buildings
amazing is that a turtle shell Metro
right there Teena we we fit in this is
our Metro we're
Turtles are we living in the
future wo look at that it's like all
wavy and liny and they didn't add extra
metal to in between the metals
now that's
futuristic and this tall building has
like it's cool shaped that is cool
shaped it looks like it's almost going
to fall over in the
GoPro and that one is a block but the
windows are different in the middle
we're in shenen
[Music]
next station open on the left please
find the gap between the train
and new Metro Shen Zen got a lot of
lines on this one too we made it to
shenzen we made it to our hotel time for
a room
tour oh you know small basic and there's
a hand with a
microphone what the heck how'd you find
me I I like that we have three beds here
this is one of them in the middle it's
actually one of the softer ones what do
you mean should we do a bed test right
now oh jeez I'm going to break my collar
bone this hotel didn't allow smoking but
it's got a bit of a smoking must it's
not bad no it was like the cheapest one
we could find here but it wasn't like
super cheap either it was probably like
closing on 40 bucks high 30s wait we
should look at the view
First Holy no nards that's incredible
that's even that's an wow I can really
see you
completely I can see like your legs have
definition stay there yeah I it's the
room suddenly became super white and
that's not just because of your
shirt the Privacy is not uh very epic in
the bathroom no wait go in the shower
entering the shower right now I'm in the
shower you're in the shower yeah I can
see you still and now I am heading over
to the toilet and I am sitting I can see
you sitting there oh no and for double
viewing I can see it even better from
the side in the
mirror so you're saying if I had my
pants off right now I would see a winus
but you know what that is that's just
Progressive yeah you know you got to be
okay with everything am all right maybe
it's better if the lights are off
probably
yeah yeah a shower I still see you so
clearly what about when I'm on the duke
or oh I can't see like anything when
you're on the dooker hey that's good
there's really a lot there's a huge
crack in the door feel like the smell's
going to leak
through oh gosh going need to crack a
window all right let's practice I'll
take a poop
quick oh pretty good the water pressure
in Trina has been pretty good that's
like positive and it comes with
heating that's not as impressive I was
expecting Iceland quality just pretend
to pee or I could just look through here
actually yeah that's our hotel in
shenzen we're not complaining we picked
the cheapest one because it's an
expensive place and uh if we want to go
places like this we got to stay in
places like this so we just like to do
add a little comedy to it to make a
lighthearted jokes on our cheap hotels
I'm trying to open this window and it's
and yeah that's our room but the best
part about this place is not the room
clearly it's the loation that is so
clear it's like there's nothing there I
told you the location was popping look
at this it's so nice outside right now
it's so nice why wasn't it like this the
entire time it would have been so much
better come on Guang Joo why was it so
cold there come on Shen Zen's just
better yeah even that's how it works
it's been a long day it took a really
long time to get here and it's not that
far it's a tall building wow look at
that thing I bet there's a lot of
pictures of that online is that the
really really tall
one do you see another very tall one in
the skyline
anywhere I don't see any tall other tall
ones I think that's one of the tallest
buildings in the world every city in
Asia just has one of these I'm not even
impressed anymore what the FR all right
let's we're just going to walk around
this area get some food and because
we've literally eaten nothing today
other than snacks so food time baby
I don't have my rice yet so I'm going to
wait to eat that I'm going to start with
these things don't know what the heck
this is it's some sort of purple Taro
rice cake looking fracker hopefully it's
good this happened yesterday when we
ordered food the food comes out before
the rice comes out and usually eat the
food with the rice like this beef but we
can't eat it yet so hopefully it doesn't
get cold but this is rice so I can eat
it with this right yeah oh
wow
W it's like a very warm mushy rice cake
with what I believe is this Taro flavor
inside it's a very slight Taro sweetness
it's kind of good the texture really
fills your whole mouth and this is just
another one of those unique possibly
cantones food it seems like a lot of the
food here is
Cantonese oh yeah hopefully that Rice
comes rice has arriv also the rice has
been really good here it's very sticky
look at that I mean it's stayed in a
ball form it's slowly shrink
ifying wow look at that this one had two
Chili Peppers let's see how spicy it is
I can smell some spice I got beef last
night too at the Vietnamese restaurant
and that was really tasty so how is this
going to Fair we haven't run into too
many spicy foods here like even the ones
that had two chili signs that I've
gotten weren't that spicy
beef put some rice projectile out to the
bottom
oh it's really hot oh jeez this a
spicy it doesn't look like an enjoyable
experience really it sucks because it's
beef so I got to chew the beef but it's
really back of the throat spice like
really back of the throat like it's not
even on my tongue or mouth at all it's
just back here I'm trying to breathe and
the rice keeps sucking into my throat
and the rice is really hot that is a bad
start to a delicious food that's really
good I don't know what the actual name
was I just saw the picture and it
translated into some sort of Chinese
name beef it's delicious it's a very
nice spice too I actually really enjoy
that kind of spice ice spice ice spice
and everything I don't know any of
herong hey myce spice that's what she
sounds like too I think that's really
good the the food here has been really
good and that is no exception and that's
spicy and I like spicy stuff sometimes
to an extent did this come out of my
mouth I think so and this and
this I got a stir fried rice cake thing
in like some cabbage something that
looks so interesting I've never seen
anything like that just a white slabs
with sauce on them I don't know if I'm
supposed to eat this with something or
what I mean it's already rice what would
you eat it with yeah true true I got the
vegetable right on
there really hot okay it's like a rice
cake and then with I think it's that
same vegetable that we see all around
here and I think it was called a water
cabbage so it kind of has a bit of a
slight saltiness to it pretty good
pretty mild it's very satisfying to chew
it's kind of like H the Korean one but a
healthier version probably it's not
sauce and we also got some shaoang bow
here I don't know I think this was the
sauce that came with hopefully it's not
tea sh long
bow it might be a risky move soup
dumpling right in the
[Music]
kisser don't worry you have hot tea to
wash it down if it's too hot are your
taste buds
fried they're really good how is it
compared to dim tyon I don't know it's
so hot
what a meal some more Cantonese food I
don't know if
this this is cantones it's something
it's from somewhere and it's in canton's
area the food's good we always get a
huge array of things and it's epic
that's a common thing here it seems like
you buy a lot of small things or you get
one big dish and then share it with a
lot of people and get some side dishes
it's the best way to do it what the fck
are those mozi sticks let's see what's I
don't know what's inside of them the
translation did not necessarily work the
best what was it something thing about
pulp and glutenous rice I don't know if
it's going to be sweet salty it's the
pulp of a
[Applause]
cow it's sweet and then there's some
sort of like sugary syrup type thing in
the middle like a chocolate but it
doesn't taste like chocolate oh wow
there's a lot of it what the heck what
flavor is
it so
hot I just burnt the tip of my tongue I
did that too I'm the hot tea ow that
hurt so you're saying we should poke
holes in all of them yes definitely it's
interesting to have the mixture of a
fried food and then a rice cake to coat
it and then you just get a nice purse of
Sweetness in there very delicious now oh
my gosh my the tip of my tongue is dead
I can't taste anything anymore I poked
holes at all of them that's good future
people will not be burned thanks to my
mishap that's always good don't drink
that tea right out of the thing either
it's really hot very
delicious the dumplings were just as
good as Den tyong if not a little better
I really like them once my tongue was
not dying from being burned these things
are interesting I don't think it's good
for a meal for one
person split it amongst the family like
once you eat about 10 of them you're
sick of them that was a review of a
restaurant that had now long
long right on the tourist Street and it
cost us a total of 174 not too bad we've
had more
[Music]
expensive welcome to the land of
chocolate Coco Park in Shen I really
didn't know what to expect I saw a
picture of this area online but it was
just called Coco Park and the metro
station is just shopping park and uh
it's pretty dang cool actually I have
one critique of shenzen already the
Metro Self ticketing machines don't work
with alip pay at least four in Ali pay
so we have to go up to the ticket
counter every time we buy tickets and
sometimes there's like a big line or
like it seems like it like is a bit
inconvenient for them and for us it's
very unfortunate Wang Joo has a plus one
for the Metro right there
wa that's a tall building why do they
always make the color scheme red I swear
they want it to look
evil what the heck China oh that one's
rainbow that's more epic and there's a
Burger King right there that's the most
epic thing of all is that the pack with
Jackson Wang right there I think it is
or just four random people for Giorgio
armanii that's not it's cool is Pan the
pack Pan the pack tell the maters that
we made it uhhuh uhhuh well they have a
live performance at this place they have
a uh geny Sushi over there those are
everywhere in China somehow there's a
frack and dragon that kind of looks like
a worm a
bit you can't tell me that's not a worm
SL caterpillar for AER I've never seen a
long Dragon like that me
neither Dairy
[Music]
Queen you can definitely tell Zen gets
more foreign tourists than
guango Taco Bell we saw Shake Shack down
there there's Dairy Queen you get milk
with whatever
you what the heck oh it's the breakfast
menu oh you get a glass of milk that's
interesting that's pretty cheap
5.9 Taco we got to hit Taco Bell we
thought it was KFC but it's Taco Bell
Taco Bell this place is pretty
cool I'm curious to see what city will
like more Jo or shenzen and I have to
say usually we end up liking the city
that's less
touristy yeah so we'll see which one it
is this time we'll let you know at the
end of the series wow look at him he's
like Bob the way he's handling that
Hammer
Hammer can we volunteer to do
this I want
[Music]
to
oh oh that is quite the loud
wow impressive hammering skills
sir he's
mesmerized he's going through his life
his past life where he was a rice
[Music]
hammerer hey how's it going where were
you the rice hammer it brought me back
to my past life as a rise hermer
[Music]
he's making
waffles
donkey
ice
wowzers it's time to
oo I don't know what that is uh prison
outfit sticks oh I like
it
strawberries and strawberry
sauce now all it's missing is the
sprinkles there they go
oh yeah sprinkle it up
perfect okay thank you look at that
freaking thing baby hi uh waffles you
know what is
[Music]
this the texture of a a birthday candle
oh I think it is a candle you're
supposed to light it strawberry
sprinkles waffle this how you do it take
some po it in oh and then
[Music]
WAFF pretty good with donkey approve
donkey is always making waffles and when
it's not for
breakfast this is what's for dessert I
don't know what that means but I still
don't know what the heck this is the
waffle is crunchy and warm
and it pop right off in a little balls
that's convenient we got one of these in
MA cow but they were just a flavored
waffle instead of actually being filled
with anything a bubble waffle yeah it's
better with ice cream even too this was
35 yeah 35 so thought it was 25 he had a
mask on so it sounded like he said 25
but he said 35 but uh yeah let's go oh
my
nuts it's a fracking worm it's got to be
a caterpillar right there's a even a
tail over there it has two tails yeah
it's a caterpillar a creepy caterpillar
creepy caterpillar
I see
[Music]
cream did you make a
friend yes did you make a friend sir yes
what's his name caddy the caterpillar
that's a creative name it's almost like
you took the animal's name and just
added a y to part of it no oh I've never
done that in my life
ducky it's caddy caddy the
caterpillar sometimes caddy talks a lot
and then they call him a chatty caddy
chatty caddy the caterpillar I'm going
to go under his arm be
careful it doesn't say don't go under
his arm though oh I don't want to get
arrested going to jail in China new
video now will I'm going to pop caddy
think you can claw this with my nail
there's only one way to find
out I'm very sof make sure you touch me
okay
pal that scared me so much the first
time I hit this thing I thought it would
be soft it's really really hard
scam this was at the thing yesterday the
green things yeah yeah what the heck is
that
there's a lot of long weight restaurants
up here this one has a big weight this
one has a bigger weight this a fancy
area this must be the fancy area that's
a buffet China
Buffet I used to love that place
Daddy come to me
son I'm very confused like is this
supposed to is he supposed to go in and
then it's supposed to come out and then
that somehow his tail comes out from
over there and then it's
it doesn't connect very well I don't
think cuz that's the end that's
definitely the end and it goes boom boom
boom but from under there I don't know
where it goes the most logical place
would be just like right into his
stomach but then he has this they
somebody messed up they should have put
it like that one over there also do
caterpillars have arms and little claws
they have like a thousand arms but uh
maybe not like they should there wait
there's one right there too oh yeah what
this is a weird animal maybe this is
some Chinese animal we don't know about
dra drag a pillar that's
new we're at the walking Street right
now it's a very interesting street guys
the Metro just closed behind that's the
little Metro station right there and
right
here uh it's uh 850 and the Metro just
closed we're very confused I don't know
if it's just this station or what it's
the like main station of the blue and
the green line it was really busy
station too I don't know how we could
close that earlier what we're going to
do tomorrow if we're out longer than
8:50 which we've been out every single
day later than that there're just uh
ticktockers right behind us we're in
like Tik Tock Nation there's literally
one over
here there's one right here and there's
this girl right here there's a guy
dressed up in like Arab garments over
there doing some weird stuff he's got a
crowd we got to go see what's going on
over there let's go people are live
streaming him doing a live stream this
is live stream setion right here I think
we've gotten to the point in society
where things are just falling apart
people are filming other people live
streaming themselves in public and now
somebody's live streaming me talking to
the
camera what a weird oh my gosh that's
the fanciest McDonald's I think we've
ever seen the coolest looking McDonald's
ever that's awesome we got to
investigate this now too also I think
that was a Chinese man I think he can
wear Arab clothes if he wants to but uh
very interesting to do that we cannot do
that as white people from America
specifically wow it's all about live
streaming here they even got their ring
lights oh he's going on the head he's
got a helmet that's
[Music]
weak ouch that's so interesting
there's people live streaming and
talking to their stream while recording
street performers who are live
[Music]
streaming wow this is like some I don't
even know if it's this open or what type
of uh postmodernist Society we're in
right now it's just people live
streaming other people live streaming
it's just content being content on
content on content and then people are
just sitting at home watching this are
they also live streaming while they're
watching this and we're making a video
out of this so you guys can watch in the
future I don't know what's
happening this is the world we live in
today we didn't see anything like this
in wjo so this is definitely some sort
of like Tech Hub City and then it's
right next to Hong Kong which probably
has more access to sign of the more
social media on the outside so this is
an interesting place so far this is very
very unique First Impressions we're
getting look at how many people are
recording
[Music]
that woman's talking through a mic to
something
else this is crazy that woman's
recording and this guy's recording
himself as the I wow this this area
right here itself is more bizarre than
Japan was and we thought Japan would be
very bizarre I am very shocked Foreigner
shocked by this
place we've made it to the McDonald's
look at this fracking thing holy nuts we
got to go on the inside to see if
there's anything special right I mean
Shen Zen there's been new Chains new
foods new restaurants that we never
thought were in China so I mean that
menu could be different usually when
stuff changes like that it's when we go
to a different like region of a country
or just straight up a different country
but we just went 30 minutes south of a
city and all of a sudden it's just
different so let's see what this fren
thing has now this is fancy
I can read this I can read that actually
hamburger this is Dragon material they
kill the dragon to receive this oh it's
a mcafe my favorite section of
McDonald's it smells like
coffee here we go oh this is very
reminiscent to the Hong Kong fancy one
oh gosh so far their advertisements look
exactly the same New Year yeah that's
exactly the same yep double Angus thick
Burger Max dude let's get it thank you
very much can I add extra thickness oh
no you can't add anymore dang it but you
can have this is Fring epic
dude this place is pretty busy still
even though the Metro is closed and half
of the
stores this is crazy but it's just a
cool outdoor mall walking area
basically similar to the one in W Jo
that was really empty at
it's like the bus of Beijing road but
more similar to the other walking street
that I will not name because it was very
long a 3D
billboard hey that's a street and wait a
second holy
Nars we're speed walking oh my gosh it's
happening all for one thing this is the
greatest day of my
life this is the greatest day Myra in
life do you see this thing this will not
stop me not
[Music]
today hop just
kidding oh it's a
cat that's not what I'm here
for oh we made it it's po the
panda Walmart virsion it's kind of ugly
what else do we know about China
than Kung Fu Panda he's kind of tall
like long he he lost some weight this is
after he became the kungu warrior the
Dragon Warrior give me your
pinky no oh wait wait
wait
scoo sugar cane
juice uh looks like there's a street
food area in here interesting mango oh
yummy a lot ofra
this area is crazy what the heck is
this well guys there's a lot of stuff
here this is overwhelming I don't know
how late this is going to be open but it
seems like it would be open all night
but who knows in China it seems like
things will randomly just shut down at
like 10:00 it's just past 9 and some
areas of this are not busy at all and
some are really busy it's weird this is